AFSCME, District Council 37 Records WAG.265
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series III: Legal Department Records, 1956-1986.
  - Butler v. DC 37: Background Materials, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Charges against DC 37 Members, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Commission to Take Deposition, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Constitution and Financial Standards Codes, DC 37 and Local 420, 1971, 1975, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Depositions, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Depositions, Local 420 Members, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Discovery, 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Drafts, ca.1979 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Hospital Crisis and May 1st Rally, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Local 420 Members' Petition, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Notes and Research, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Order to Show Cause, Butler Deposition, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Order to Show Cause, O'Malley Deposition, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings I, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings II, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings III, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings IV, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings V, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings VI, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings VII, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings VIII, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings IX, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings X, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings XI, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Preliminary Injunction, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Protective Order and Appeal, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Reply Brief, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Summary of Argument, ca.1979 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Summaries and Complaint, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Temporary Restraining Order, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - City Civil Service Commission, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Citywide Bargaining: Deferral Payment Agreement and Comparison Agreement I, 1982-1983 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Citywide Bargaining: Deferral Payment Agreement and Comparison Agreement II, 1982-1983 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Citywide Bargaining: Deferral Payment Agreement and Comparison Agreement, Drafts I, 1982-1983 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Citywide Bargaining: Deferral Payment Agreement and Comparison Agreement, Drafts II, 1982-1983 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Citywide Bargaining: Municipal Coalition Economic Agreement, Drafts, 1982-1983 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - DC 37 and CUNY, Board of Higher Education Arbitration (Eugene Sanjour Case): Background Materials, 1968-1977 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - DC 37 and CUNY, Board of Higher Education Arbitration (Sanjour Case): Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - DC 37 and CUNY, Board of Higher Education Arbitration (Sanjour Case): Legal Papers, 1977-1978 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - DC 37 and CUNY, Board of Higher Education Arbitration (Sanjour Case): Notes, ca.1977 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - DC 37 and Local 1549 v. New York Police Department (NYPD): Transcripts I, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - DC 37 and Local 1549 v. NYPD: Transcripts II, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - DC 37 and Local 1549 v. NYPD: Transcripts III, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - DC 37 and Local 1549 v. NYPD: Transcripts IV, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - DC 37 and Local 1549 v. NYPD: Transcripts V, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - DC 37 and Local 1549 v. NYPD: Transcripts VI, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - DC 37 v. Commission of Investigation of the State of New York (SIC) (Release Time Program Case): Affidavit of Cause, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Background Material, 1973-1981 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Background Material, Legal I, undated, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Background Material, Legal II, undated, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Correspondence, 1957-1982 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Decision, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Legal Drafts, undated (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Legal Drafts, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Motion to Compel, Memoranda in Opposition, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Motion to Compel, Memoranda in Support, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Motion to Compel, Reply Briefs, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Motion to Quash, Affidavits in Opposition, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Motion to Quash, Affidavits in Support, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Motion to Quash, Memoranda in Opposition, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Motion to Quash, Memoranda in Support, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Municipal Labor Committee (MLC) Member List, ca.1981 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Order to Show Cause, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: SIC Annual Reports, 1961-1979 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Subpoenae, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Transcripts, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Executive Orders (Mayoral), 1973-1980 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Financial Emergency Act: Legal Notes and Memoranda, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Financial Emergency Act: Proposed Legislation I, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Financial Emergency Act: Proposed Legislation II, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Fiscal Crisis: Effect on Women and Minorities, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Government and Civic Employees Organizing Committee: DC 37 Merger, 1956-1957 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Local 211 (Allied Building Inspectors Union) Summer Hours Arbitration: Background Materials, 1967-1977 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Local 211 (Allied Building Inspectors Union) Summer Hours Arbitration: Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Local 211 (Allied Building Inspectors Union) Summer Hours Arbitration: Legal Papers, 1977-1978 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Local 211 (Allied Building Inspectors Union) Summer Hours Arbitration: Notes, ca.1977 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Local 211 (Allied Building Inspectors Union) Summer Hours Arbitration: Transcripts, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Local 371 (SSEU) v. Adam Walinsky, Chairman of SIC, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Disaffiliation Proposal, 1976, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Disaffiliation Proposal, Background Materials I, 1957-1980 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Disaffiliation Proposal, Background Materials II, 1957-1980 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Legal Papers, 1974-1978 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Local 2021 (OTB): Arbitration of Grievance, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Mando, Daniel J., et al. v. Abraham Beame, et al. (Emergency Employment Act Employees Case): Briefs and Memoranda of Law, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Mando v. Beame: Correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Mando v. Beame: Exhibits I, 1971-1974 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Mando v. Beame: Exhibits II, 1971-1974 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Mando v. Beame: Exhibits III, 1971-1974 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Mando v. Beame: Exhibits IV, 1971-1974 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Mando v. Beame: Exhibits V, 1971-1974 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Mando v. Beame: Extra Legal, 1974-1976 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Mando v. Beame: Factual, 1971-1974 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Mando v. Beame: Notes and Memoranda, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Mando v. Beame: Pleadings I, 1972-1974 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Mando v. Beame: Pleadings II, 1972-1974 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Mando v. Beame: Pleadings III, 1972-1974 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Mando v. Beame: Transcripts, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - MENTOR Program (MELS and Board of Education), 1984 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - MENTOR Program (MELS and Board of Education): Printed Material, undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Middlebrooks, et al. v. NYPD (Police Aides Case): Charts and Statistical Analysis, 1976-1979 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Middebrooks v. NYPD: Documents and Exhibits, 1978-1980 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Middebrooks v. NYPD: Formal Papers, 1980-1981 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Middebrooks v. NYPD: Labor-Management Meeting, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Middebrooks v. NYPD: Legal Research, 1975-1979 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Middebrooks v. NYPD: Notes, ca.1980 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Middebrooks v. NYPD: Statistics on Coverage, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Middebrooks v. NYPD: Witnesses, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - New York City Board of Education: CETA Titles, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - New York City Board of Education: Improper Labor Practices, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - New York City Board of Education: Stavisky-Goodman Litigation, 1976-1980 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation HHC: Conflict of Interest Cases, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - New York City HHC: General Legal, 1970-1976 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - New York City HHC: General Legal, 1977-1978 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - New York City HHC: General Legal, 1979-1984 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - New York Police Department: Improper Labor Practices, 1979-1980 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Parking Violations Bureau, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity: AFSCME et al. v. State of Washington, Clippings, 1983-1984 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Pay Equity: AFSCME v. Washington, Comparable Worth Studies, 1974, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Pay Equity: AFSCME v. Washington, Petition for En Banc Hearing, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Pay Equity: AFSCME v. Washington, Pleadings, 1983-1985 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Pay Equity: AFSCME v. Washington, Press Releases, 1982-1985 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Pay Equity: AFSCME v. Washington, Settlement, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Pay Equity: AFSCME Publications, undated, 1980-1981 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Pay Equity: AFSCME Research Department Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Pay Equity: Chicago, AFSCME EEOC Filing, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Pay Equity: Comparable Worth Articles I, undated, 1980-1986 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Pay Equity: Comparable Worth Articles II, undated, 1980-1986 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Pay Equity: Comparable Worth Research Materials, 1980-1986 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Pay Equity: Gold, Michael Evans, "A Dialogue on Comparable Worth", 1984 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Pay Equity: Gross, Beverly, 1984-1985 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Pay Equity: Law Review Articles, 1982-1985 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Pay Equity: Los Angeles County Employees, SEIU Report, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Pay Equity: Minnesota Department of Employee Relations, Local Government Pay Equity Supplement for Cities, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Pay Equity: New York City, 1982-1985 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Pay Equity: New York City Office of the Mayor, Report on Status of Women in NYC Government, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Pay Equity: New York State Comparable Worth Study by Center for Women in Government, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Pay Equity: New York State Division of Human Rights, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Pay Equity: Newman, Winn Articles and Statements, undated, 1981-1985 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Pay Equity: Printed Material (Various Organizations), 1979-1985 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity: U.S. Commission on Civil Rights Reports, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Pay Equity: U.S. Commission on Civil Rights, Winn Newman Testimony, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity: U.S. General Accounting Office, Status of State Activities on Pay Equity, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity: Women's Advocacy Committee of New York, Study on Women in NYC Government (Clerical Workers), 1972 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Santos, Rafael v. Security and Law Enforcement Employees, 1978-1978 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Santos, Rafael v. Security and Law Enforcement Employees: Background Materials, undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - School Breakfast Program, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - School Breakfast Program: Community School Board Lists/Compliance, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - School Breakfast Program: Response to Demand Letter, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - School Breakfast Program: Legal Research, 1974-1976 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Tellez, Rogelio v. City of New York, 1975-1982 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Wage Controls, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor: Bargaining Rights, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Women in City Government United, et al. v. City of New York, et al.: Administrative, 1977-1983 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Background Materials, 1973, 1976-1977, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Background Materials, Legal, undated, 1971-1979 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Background Materials, Legislation, 1971, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Background Materials, Pension Plan, 1969-1970 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Background Materials, Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association (TIAA), 1975, 1981-1982 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Change of Attorney, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Class Action Status, 1975-1976 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Clippings, 1973-1980 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Correspondence I, 1973-1983 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Correspondence II, 1973-1983 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Internal Memoranda, 1973-1976 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Interrogatories I, 1975-1977, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Interrogatories II, 1975-1977, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Interrogatories III, 1975-1977, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Kinzel Commission Reports, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Memoranda I, 1975-1978, 1980-1982 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Memoranda II, 1975-1978, 1980-1982 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Memoranda III, 1975-1978, 1980-1982 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Motion for Summary Judgment, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Notes, 1976-1979 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Notice to Admit and Responses, 1976-1977, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Order to Show Cause, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Pleadings I, 1975-1982 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Pleadings II, 1975-1982 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Pleadings III, 1975-1982 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Program Planners Analysis, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Settlement Proposals I, 1977-1980 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Settlement Proposals II, 1977-1980 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Stipulations, 1975-1977, 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Transport Workers Union Case (Burns, Jackson, Miller, Summit, and Spitzer v. Lindner), MLC Amicus Curiae, undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Workers' Compensation, 1977-1984 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Youth Employment Act: Young Adult Conservation Corps, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Series IV: Communications Department Records, 1963-2004.
  - Subseries IV:A: Edward Handman Records, 1972-1991.
    - City Budget: Clippings, 1978-1980 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Common Retirement Fund, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Contract Negotiations, 1980, 1987, 1990-1991 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Contract Negotiations: Clippings, 1977-1978 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Contract Negotiations: Clippings, 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Contract Negotiations: Clippings, 1987, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Contract Negotiations: Municipal Labor Committee Campaign, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: General, 1983-1989 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - DC 37 Film Strip, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - DC 37/AFL-CIO Conference: "Changing Situation of Workers and Their Unions", 1985 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - DC 37/AFL-CIO Conference: "Changing Situation of Workers and Their Unions": Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - DC 37/AFL-CIO Conference: "Changing Situation of Workers and Their Unions": Transcript, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1975): Chronology, 1974-1977 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1975): Clippings, undated (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1975): Clippings, 1973-1974 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1975): Clippings, Jan 1975-Jul 1975 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1975): Clippings, Aug 1975-Dec 1975 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1975): Clippings, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1975): General, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1975): Municipal Labor Committee Reports, ca.1976 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, Oct 1990-Nov 1990 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, Dec 1990-Jan 1991 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, Feb 1991-Mar 1991 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, Apr 1991 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, May 1, 1991-May 15, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, May 16, 1991-May 31, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, Jun 1, 1991-Jun 20, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, Jun 21, 1991-Jun 30, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, Jul 1991-Aug 1991 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): General, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): General, Jan 1991-Mar 1991 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): General, Apr 1991-Jun 1991 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Library Budget Cuts (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Handman, Edward: Biographical Information, undated (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Handman, Edward: Book Proposal, undated (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Handman, Edward: Journalism Syllabi, undated (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Handman, Edward: Op-Ed Articles, undated (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Handman, Edward: Op-Ed Articles, 1984-1990 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Handman, Edward: Testimony on State Government, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - It's Your City, It's Our Job Radio Show: Journalism Contests, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - It's Your City, It's Our Job Radio Show Transcripts (Domestic Violence; Staten Island; Homeless), 1987-1989 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Labor Movement: Clippings, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Labor-Management Articles, undated, 1985, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - March on Washington for Jobs and Job Security, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - March on Washington for Jobs and Job Security: Clippings, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Political Action: Mayoral Campaign (Dinkins), 1990 (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Political Action: Presidential Campaign (Mondale-Ferraro), 1984 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Public Relations Campaign, undated, 1972, 1986-1988 (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - Reagan Budget: Clippings, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 33)
    - Reagan Budget: Impact on New York City, 1980-1984 (Box 40, Folder 34)
    - Williams, Franklin: Commentaries, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 35)
    - Window Guard Campaign, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Subseries IV:B: Bill Schleicher Records, 1992-2004.
    - AFSCME Convention (36th), 2004 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Bargaining: Notes, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Black History Month, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Blackout (Con Edison), 2003 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Building-Wide Meetings: Notes, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - City Budget, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - City Budget: Child Health Nurses, 2003-2004 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Clippings, 2002-2004 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Contract Negotiations, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Contract Negotiations: Fair Contract Rally, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: AFSCME, Insurance Fraud Claims, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Albert Diop and Martin Lubin Clippings, 1998, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Annual Return/Report of Employee Benefit Plan, 1992-1993 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Clippings and Articles, 1997-2000 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Correspondence, 1995-2000 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Financial Statements, 1996-1999 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Harold Hawson and Anthony Lawson v. DC 37 et al., 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Judicial Panel Decisions, 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: KPMG, "Report on Certain Financial Activities at AFSCME DC 37 and Funds" Book 1 of 3, I, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: KPMG, "Report on Certain Financial Activities at AFSCME DC 37 and Funds" Book 1 of 3, II, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: KPMG, "Report on Certain Financial Activities at AFSCME DC 37 and Funds" Book 2 of 3, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: KPMG, "Report on Certain Financial Activities at AFSCME DC 37 and Funds" Book 3 of 3, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: KPMG, "The Ratification Vote on the 1995 Economic Agreement: A Report to the General Council of AFSCME", 1999 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Labor Organization Annual Reports, 1989-1998 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Legal Transcripts, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Notes, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Press Releases, 1999-2001 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Printed Material, 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Reform Proposals, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Union Democracy Articles, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence: General, 2001-2003 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Delegate Education, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Delegates: Meeting Notes, 2001-2004 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Direct Election of Officers Dispute: Veronica Montgomery-Costa Testimony, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - Editorials: Source Material, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - Executive Board: Meeting Notes, 2001-2002 (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - Executive Board: Meeting Notes, 2003-2004 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Event Announcements: DC 37, 2003-2004 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Event Announcements: Other Organizations, 2003-2004 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Finances: Corruption Scandals, 2002-2003 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Financial Reports, 2003-2004 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Grassroots Lobby Institute: Meeting Notes, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Group Leaders: Meeting Notes, 2001-2004 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Group Leaders: Reports, Nov 2001-Feb 2002 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Group Leaders: Reports, May 2002-Feb 2003 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Group Leaders: Reports, Apr 2003-Sep 2004 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Health Care Benefits and Prescription Drug Coverage, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Immigrant Worker Freedom Ride, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - International Human Rights Day: AFL-CIO March, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Iraq War, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Labor Day, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 15)